(Howard:)Fine. I'll wear gloves next time.
(Bernadette:)It's still gonna take a few weeks for
the hormones to leave your system.
(Howard:)I feel so stupid. And fat.
(Penny:)It's okay.
You still look great to me.
(Bernadette:)In fact, why don't we go in the
bedroom and I'll prove it to you?
(Howard:)Sex? Really? I mean,
that's just your solution to everything!
Oh, and herds a fun thing.
(Amy:)I worked it out so that there are
"planko" and "janko."
"PIanko" is a spoon with food,
'janko" is a spoon without food.
"Janko" is spelled
with a silent "ptang."
(Amy:)Sheldon, you're not even listening
to the rules of my made-up language.
(Sheldon:)-Yes, I am.
-Then what does "tweepadock" mean?
(Leonard:)Uh...
(Sheldon:)Elephant?
(Amy:)Lucky guess.